We're two explanations of procedures of meeting, but we're not out here tonight.
We want to want to have often to ask the questions, and we're going to go over the rest of those procedures.
We're three occasions.
I'm proud of that.
I'm proud of the first adjournment.
Thank you so much for coming in to the service and the service.
We're blessed to be in a welcoming situation.
Why do you know that we're going to make it clear to you?
You see it.
We're obviously going to do that.
So you asked me to take a specific message.
But this meeting was really good.
We're going to express it to all of the folks in the room.
Thank you for what we are.
Good night.
Good evening.
Good afternoon.
Good night.
Welcome to the University of MCMO Rich.
Thank you Maya, with the members of the Council.
A big new adult.
It's really appreciate.
You're going out of your way and you're going to have to work right at nine, you're going to come here with us, talk about all the things that are really important for our career.
My name is Maurice, I'm the city manager of my own, and I'm certainly very honored to be here.
So I'm going to start by introducing the folks we have here on the stage, so we're going to go through tonight and we'll have a video of who's speaking.
First up, I'm going to introduce Larry Gordon, who I'll track at the top of our NLP. He's the leading counsel of the 2008 State Civilification.
Mr. Gordon also serves as a consultant of the current license and realized the team of legal management.
Larry has been involved in these matters for many, many years, from the mid-eighths, and the capital wealth of information.
And most importantly, he is just an extraordinary defender of the system.
Next we have Walker Stoskey, Walker from the Sociedent Attorney, the Davis Wright from Maine, Philadelphia, also a AA, a DFT, the DFT, so our primary team will be current 1992 license, a complaining DCM field in the realizing of the team, sort of.
Next we have Brent Bradsteth, a great grass field, a mayor of the...
We also have pretty shoulders.
Reading was the mayor of May 11, 2014, 2011.
And we had mayor one's partner, who was mayor
or 2020.
Also, we had a city journey in the middle of the year.
But that year.
Also, I'd like to recognize the folks in the audience
in addition to Nick and Terry and we have witness.
We have a couple of staff members who are present in the mini-OADM.
And we have the mayor who might not.
We have Commissioner Mike versus Mr. Gordon.
We also have Russell Pearls.
Mr. Chairman, too.
In addition, we have...
We have council members members here today.
We have day to day to support.
Right, he's seven, four, one.
We have a double reward.
And I can't go without recognizing
some very poor dignitaries.
A great opportunity to be community to witness tonight.
And that is Chief Cook from the Ottawa Tribe.
He's with us.
We have Chief Wallace.
He's returning also with us.
And we have Chief Lake.
I don't know what I'm saying.
So that being said.
Subscribe.
What's going to move on?
We're going to get an option.
This is for the presentations.
The very work is going to give a presentation
on a ceiling nation.
The end of March.
Three, two, three, two, three.
We'll give a short presentation.
Let's speak on their experiences.
And if I didn't know that I'd work with the officers,
we would give a final presentation tonight
before we move on.
So it's that thing we said.
One more thing before we begin.
And the passing begins to put police
on the side of your boat.
So we don't wish we have any of our public members.
We want to make sure that we hear everyone.
So we're reporting this.
Putting it out.
We hear that.
And so that.
This time we can start.
We can turn it over there.
I think we can turn it over there.
Actually, this is the case.
I don't want to make it think it's a good idea.
We have another one.
Actually, we have the car.
We can turn it over there.
I do second.
This is a extreme political time.
This is a city.
And we've all worked here a time.
We've all worked here a time.
I'm going to appreciate the year when I think you can't just show us the deal with the
ambition of doing something.
Second thing before you get in my substance, I literally have a great presentation and
a better result.
This is just an amazing result.
We folks are so lucky to have an opportunity to use this kind of structure, because it is
extremely unique in my experience.
Now, as stated a peer, we are really going to focus on the state-central education.
There are three areas of focus in hearing about those tonight, and it's probably not something
that has been going to happen to me.
So, there's discussion about, you know, finding a peer and a dispute with G.I.D.A.
But it's more of a fine decision, more of a fine process.
I am the primary journey for the state-central education.
That's the 2008 flood case, if we hear about it.
It's where the citizens of Miami or Miami are soon.
G.I.D.A. is an aggressive act.
We are trying to hold G.I.D.A responsible for what they have done.
It's not defending the city.
It's not protecting the city.
This is possible to make out and trying to hold G.I.D.A.
I've been litigating with G.I.D.A since 1994.
It was the first lawsuit.
I started being involved in 1993, so I'm pushing through the years.
G.I.D.A. is a very sophisticated atmosphere.
I mean, you know what they're doing?
I'm going to hire the right people.
This is not an easy task.
And they are very set on making this as difficult as possible.
Or the citizens of Miami.
And for that matter, I really want to emphasize.
This is she doesn't stop at the city coming on her to city one.
It's very much as an issue in the capital.
Much of the flooding is actually more than a loss in the county than it is in the city.
So don't view.
I know this is the city oriented presentation.
And it's appropriate for it to be.
You don't think that this is going to be a city problem.
Very, if you've never been involved in being able to try and make these papers,
the name would be probably a question that apparently could be in the case.
And I think the 2015 years of high-run understanding of the mine,
it's been such a good plan.
There's no reason to help you.
I hope that's it.
And I want to take a second, just to really focus on what I'm about to say.
My focus on what team is signed.
None of them are my words.
I am an advocate for the city.
I firmly believe in the city's position.
But these are not conclusions they find in them.
They're not conclusions they find in the city.
These are criminals.
decisions that were made by courts that added some cases days and days or weeks of testimony presented to them.
Most of the courts, not the one, and then we're going to go back to the men on the list of the documents that were created
at the 40s and 60s, but the city had zeroing, but it's nothing that the city has ever given.
These are new tools. It's a black and beach engineering, a better engineering company, the court engineers,
that are coming to the conclusions that I'm about to show them.
So don't think this is the city that trying to argue or trying to present a try to advocate to.
What are what we are doing is showing the facts of the map so that as you go forward with more analysis of evaluation of what's happening,
you can have a factual scientific firm foundation on where you're going.
And there is one conclusion that can be held once you get through this process.
That's the whole damn, is significantly flooding the city of mind.
There is significantly down caused, not natural flooding, that is the cause by principal dam.
And that's then concluded by multiple boards, by multiple engineers.
And that is absolute rock solid fat, and I hope we come to that conclusion as you look at this material.
So if you get into what, of course, the German, and I actually, because of the commentary that I've seen going around town,
I added material that I didn't add in the slide.
One of the very first times of the decision of whether GRDA was causing what's called back water, but what's called damn caused, what.
It was way back in 1943.
I heard that the data of why I was going to town, mere coincidence, but the very first case that involved GRDA,
whether they were causing damn caused flooding, was the school district board of education.
Here's what's called, the Oklahoma Supreme Court concluded in 1943.
So we're talking nearly eight years now.
The rendered down of 40 is liable for damages caused by backing up flood water.
When it added, not required to write compounds such water above such water.
And, yeah, the GRDA is not obeyed from my ability.
By the reason of the fact that it was required to, and did follow the instructions of the federal authorities,
and so back and back to the waters, it doesn't such level.
Those federal authorities in this context would be even cold.
So when you hear GRDA site, it's not our fault.
It's the court, which is fine.
is operating in 7.5 to 9A's and the produce power of all costs.
This doesn't result in our mandate, but there's a good plan.
7.5 level also promotes residential and commercial development.
7.45 level, middle of the larger market,
our liberal identity, and the Marines, and the one percent.
But does it cost line on the citizens?
Well, there's also, as my continued issues,
the girls from the club can't get in to this kind of people
that are having orders to get into the list of purchases.
In turn, that amount of development.
We're non-listened, say, there's lots.
I started on there that amount of development work.
And it's always a struggle to be non-listened,
plus the power of respect to companies that come to our community.
Damaged in infrastructure in the homes, the city pool, the fairs,
as well, and this is all the homes in the rest of us,
so we'll go back to the next one.
If the prices are probably 9% of that,
it's 7% of us.
It's almost 10% of us, but that's quite a blessing.
It's over 4.5.
In this part, in this part, in this part,
we're supposed to be a significant period of thought of any more of us.
As a result, hundreds of homes in the land are now
the floodways that are never very much like home before.
And any of those homes that have access to the mortals
are now required about that all-all-all-all.
Go to buy a house for four-inch revenue,
that's an income that you'll attract with a half-inch of a penny
to afford or put another half-inch half-inch of a month.
That guy's wish was to select any of the budget insurance
of proper tax.
The amount of them have cost of flood insurance
you can afford up to 20% less of the tax than other markets on average.
Which reduces the size and quality of what you can buy from a penny.
This, the price is proper, guys.
It's a fall home to the club.
It's a versatile tax in the amount of proper tax
generated to support our students.
So a lot of them at the limit of flood money,
you don't feel like it's just a five-inch in their share
or a city tax dollars on these losses.
But there are so many to record in the right way
if the citizens are infected by this flood,
and they don't always understand it.
There's a need for more of a city as a kind of bank on property now.
The order of the system to spend on the function of the program,
our city was required to adopt the order to do those
with the use of credit loss by non-properies.
We would love it.
I voted to conclude the video about the order to spend on our service.
We had no choice at the order to dissipate in the end
after the end of the flood insurance.
Remember, many of those properties,
and you must know we're not anything.
Now, the limit of what?
If your property is in the flood planning system,
it's managed to see the 50% the city
cannot give you a permit to be had there on.
It's just going to sit there and we can not give you a learning.
And even worse, it doesn't matter what quality it can be important, it doesn't matter what kind of thing you want.
Your moment's damage to what it can be percent in your development, we can not give you a learning to do.
And that's a human thing. You know, it's only five percent energy.
You're almost out of this year. In 26 percent per year, we have to track that.
We can not give you a learning to do it. So a lot of children think about what that does your home does.
If you were now a flood by and you never want to afford it, this is going to be more or more money.
This is going to be more or more money. This is going to be more or more money.
There's going to be a long record that is already 25 percent of that I'm going to use up.
It affects our home values to that.
That can't be used if you're going to be mad at the city, it can be mad at here, whatever it is going to help with that.
But you can be mad at here, because it's their fault.
Those who just send them to that community like the Moscow or the City of Citizens, in return we're working in.
We do this more or less across.
I do the other concept that can be considered to be our community.
That's not even quite a lot of it. It's not even close.
It's not even close.
It's not just how by the city of the Gardian Foreigners, parts and commerce in nacional situation.
That will not have a nuclear reactor from forced Gardian countries.
Outside of our leader levels, the fourth factor in the war could open up anything.
In the letter center for a member of the interior in Ofinning.
Part of the apartments in the end had to be on the edge of the trap.
We've worked for years to have any other Democratic fiber, relatively mandate was being promised to display to the realizing of the project to protect the use of the dry substances.
of drugs. Although different horrible, specifically at any of the city's interstiters,
are actually so close to the right of the drug to be that the difference in your right
is the difference in your right. Last thing to do with my 70 years is there, I showed
that 10 different financial numbers, all of them went as important to continue in this fight.
It's not necessarily those who can catch a money when you're a little guy by the end of the
town in the world that haven't had the initials of our own centers on their side.
The wind you were on the side of the right and we had all of this sort of centers.
I'm going to walk this today and I know that the world will be a long time towards this part.
And I've bought my, I've bought my, I've got another one.
And also, we're continuing our life.
We can continue to ask them to vote votes to support us.
The things that you hear about the moment is,
we're always portraying the moment that we're trying to just
watch our gigs that build on the bloodline.
The insurer, the national instrument to blow insurers,
didn't come into existence until 1960,
and I don't know what the percentage of contemporary
he was built after the like 60s through the 70s,
that what really referred to about red tagging columns was
if, you know, when he had more than 50% damage,
we had to red tag with which, exactly what he said,
you're not going to be back there.
Tell somebody that they've got a business
that they can come back into your business,
suddenly they have a worthless piece of property.
And, according to what we call a really loving we,
these all these houses that came down.
Now, we've said this couple of expensive,
only yards, what are you going to do with it,
and then be locked in the water.
So, it is complex of their program I'm talking about
this yesterday at the 40s.
You know, really, it's kind of simple,
because I've always said it's very complex.
And, you're really right.
I mean, it's not.
It's easy to see issues.
It's very, very important to know the solutions.
And, I can assure you,
and I have no one.
I really have no reason to not trust you or get,
but it literally started me,
the first three guys I've got.
And, if anybody doesn't believe me,
I'm not going to get into the examples
of where seven year period you're not,
you're not going to have to get in there.
So, you know, it's one of those things
that this one really needs to be not.
This could be, this invariably,
you know, it has passed a can.
I've passed it to a really,
in the council,
passed on to the commissioners.
We just keep passing the torch.
And we just hear,
we hear nothing that it seems definitely
on going to a call from the ground.
So, February, 1995.
I was 15 years old.
The first time I was living,
we got three feet, four inches.
It was devastating.
to see your home, but one of them is just in the discussion.
The same snow, we had a ripped apartment pad out of home,
got out of sheet rock, removed insulation.
And I was 15, I'm 15 to do it then.
We still have the same problem.
We're still by, I was in by.
My house was a, let's let the two more time down to that.
Within two years, the last time, the only thing
shown was the peak of our roof.
So we couldn't, didn't move back.
So we had to move.
And we thought, we left a lot of the roof in that mess.
We left time to grow up.
My wife, she grew up in elementary school.
And in 2007, which was pre-ironically,
I was very sure that the difference between the dam and the flooding
would be 5 feet.
My wife also got 5 feet water in the house.
And that was the last time I lived in that home,
but that there are a long time.
This same story would be told by many, many, many verses,
but how they lost everything.
Many were citizens of the summer of this flooding problem today.
Their home was all they had.
That is their retirement plan.
They're not a well-meat.
Other than their home, the things in it.
And during the eight, it doesn't care about that.
They take advantage of those people over and over and over.
And they can do nothing about it, but take it.
So as a community, I feel we need to route it behind myself.
We need to be there support.
I see systems of nonsense there in the audience.
And I'm sure it's been our community for how many years.
I think I'm flooded the over and over and they keep coming back.
And our community does them.
And I know we support them.
But how many times do they have to go through that?
If the business has come in, and just like they were talking about it,
they're not going to be developing the development.
We may see stores getting flooded out.
Why would they want to bring a store here?
Why would they want to bring it out?
So this is a new addition that we've got to keep back.
Or are you going to have to do that?
I took over January 7, 2020.
But the location was a priority to me.
This ever was for a very limited building.
And within two weeks, I was down, looking out at the legislative retreat.
So round it.
I'm curious, because I was a new sucker in a pack.
It thought they had, so they made it for you,
run it, and try to see if you can get something done.
And I was getting this new sucker.
But I also made it really clear that before we knew anything,
our system's need to be taken care of.
Because our system will only get damaged over and over.
I told the answer, let's see, you know,
that I will not give our system a mark.
I will not give our system a mark.
Just to take a deal of time.
And I know the brand, the group, you know the same way.
So they hear, and I mean, I started at Maris,
led by, and we had, we got a thing on that word,
and we got a little bit of a word.
And we met with your ASL cops.
And we had some, what we thought were these are cops.
And we thought making the rest somewhere.
They hosted us at their place.
We hosted them here.
And I was happy with the video.
What is one of this.
Lessons of the most.
We took it to the parents.
And we, they asked, like, at the first time,
they never seen what we were telling.
But we were telling how high it was on our parents.
We took it to our home.
And it showed what the pool was at.
And it was kind of our walk.
Because they were looking at the building.
And they looked out the river.
They looked back at buildings.
They said, what are you going to hear?
Well, yes.
Yeah, this building you're standing side.
This could put in the walk.
And it was kind of a shock to them in our face.
I couldn't believe.
It's just one of that deep.
I mean, we drove around a several different places.
And show them their area.
But we did.
The castle where the main road is the warning to try to make a deal.
But they were looking at several times.
There.
What they wanted is that they wanted us to drop the.
That's all they cared about.
They wanted us to drop the deal.
We wouldn't do that.
To take care of our citizens.
Or sit and have a conversation.
They wanted us to.
We ended up winning the bid.
To achieve trust.
We won the bill.
And we need to start the court.
We're going to change it to the judges.
I believe it's posted online.
I mean, reading.
A lot of the law doesn't want to to address credit,
but our citizens.
To this whole many, it's what I've come to work.
So those are these.
Their opinions in this case.
I'm with.
We're going to fight.
But you can do this process.
I've been told that.
You.
You lit it.
Thanks for watching, and don't forget to like and subscribe for more videos.
and I want to see the big depiction that I should just let you guys know the ways that I want to see the big picture.
Well, you are the big picture. You are the big picture of the nice and person.
And we are the white one, the theme.
Do we want to be part of the GRDA? Absolutely. That would be great.
That would be who you are.
And I hope that GRDA will watch this video in the name of my little room round.
Go back and tell the one red.
Let's set down and do something good for our citizens.
And good for you.
Let's make a work for our community.
It can happen.
But we got set down at the table.
Good thing.
And make it happen.
We are willing.
So no citizens.
We are willing to need five people.
Let's speak with seven people.
It's great to be here.
Here was one of the biggest sherry members in our group.
So next up we have
Thank you.
Once again, it's a real honor and pleasure to be here.
I am on my own track of the short time world of the state.
I have worked actively for you all here in my room for a year.
You know, I have worked for a process in my current name.
I actually started at a point 13 with some things that we go on on the top of that.
I do a book or a different place.
When it is lawful to not to my third place,
veteran who is based in Seattle,
I don't have the offices of these kids.
And I have colleagues at the Seattle University.
So first.
I have to apologize.
Everybody up here in the scope of so quickly and from such personal experience.
And I have a great.
My presentation is covered a little on the rise.
I have a lot about the procedure.
The federal regulatory regime.
I have a lot of opportunities that this.
Once in a generation of generations,
we're licensing reasons.
I just hope you all understand a little bit of what's going on in this very complicated.
But I'll try to move more quickly to my slides that I intend to do.
You see something real about.
I think it's interesting.
I hope you'll ask questions.
And we have to be careful.
But I want to prioritize the time we go on that.
Say it.
So my big points today are as we're going to realize that the conditions on how
the ambulances are operated, those conditions are supposed to be the term
that the process is called.
And that in the end, the balance is in power output, with other factors including
that's including clinical control, and that project here.
And basically the city is struggling with the ambulances in that.
And the school that has probably put it in place where they can be
the first time in the bio-accessory.
Or, obviously, you can use the balance of interest, whether you're well in
the barrenness of life, or keep it high on the floor,
and keep it high on the floor.
And I should say, when I say it to my objective,
we're going to do the principal of the project.
That's cool at the end, basically.
And it's going to be just a kind of a regular choice to eat.
I'm being told that I need to be closer to the mic, is that better?
All right.
Thank you.
I'm sorry about that.
Thank you for being here.
So basically, we're trying to help the city restore that balance of interest
in the federal licensing process.
And give it a lot of training communities of the water,
and balance out of those players.
That's cool at the end.
That's a full hydraulic project.
That balance.
And there's a process that I've talked about.
That's much more people I've been doing.
It has basically broken that.
And it did decades ago.
I don't know.
Success to the local licensing.
I would believe we'll still take years.
But the city's efforts do seem to be starting a bear fruit.
And we'll talk about some of the size along the way.
So now we're getting a little bit of details.
Just to help you understand a little bit of what this works.
The federal power act that Congress ended up in the 1920 requires
every hydraulic power act basically all of the little sports.
To have federal license in order to generally have it done.
Those kinds of power licenses are issued by the federal identity
of the regular torque commission.
That's called the burger.
And a license lasts for 30 to 50 years.
Now, one license is issued.
The license scene has to accept all the conditions on that.
Balance those interest that I've talked about.
That for the purpose as conditions of taking the license.
And then as you near the end of the existing license,
the licensing procedures to give five years in advance.
Roughly.
So under the federal power act,
for the first issue of project.
places.
First has to find that project is the best adapted to the comprehensive plan for improving
or developing a watermelon, and because a bunch of people stuck in the law about what
comprehensive means.
But basically it means pounds.
It means not just hydropowerment.
Things that are specifically in the law and it's probably not an exhaustive list, but that
of them, these are driven into the level of power.
What control?
It's a tradition while live irrigation, commerce, and navigation, water supply, recreation,
environmental management.
Not everyone who knows the plan, every project, but that gives you a sense of the breadth
of existence that are meant to be found.
It's an expert pacified on about its digital licensing.
So that's a little framework on what federal time and power licensing is.
Now, for my firm, Davis Retro, may be the duty team.
What we're doing with this is, starts with work under the current licensing.
It says, in particular, it's issued in many times.
And colleagues of mine who are actually no longer with the firm.
But one of them is a client and a company.
Worked on issue starting on 2013, opposing key areas, it takes to raise the weight of the
rule where the firm can talk about it.
And then, at the very end of 2018, also the current licensing file, the Z-SKP1 and the
experts about how to go into a good morning deal.
The DC circuit appeal came out of that point, and we'll talk with a little of that.
And so my firm was the primary and that appeal is what, which has been successful for us.
And I should say, what I say, also this presentation.
What I mean by this, the city of Miami, and the team of the city that I visit myself part of.
So I hope that you really say to us, if I'm not clearly talking about my firm, I'm talking about
the city that we're working on.
Under the licensing, which kicked off in 2017 that sort of five year count that
into the end of the old licensing.
Now they're talking about how the city and the civil litigation is one of a hundred and
fifty-six players, and it's seeking damages for property damage and
expenses that the city occurred directly, essentially as a property on the
market, and it's not like you haven't played this.
The further licensing is very different than that.
The city is our only one.
But it's functioning not as one of many kind of individual property owners.
It's really there representing an interest in the community, just as it would
would, you know, police or public services, those sorts of things.
And success in the licensing would basically mean you were short of lower thoughts.
the city and it's kind of nervous. And it's possible it could also result in other mitigation measures that
here and here would be required to now. This is a broad range of what that could look like and those sorts
of questions to the get into kind of the second half of the realized process that we're not into yet.
Now I do want to talk a little bit about fees and device rights compensation I understand that's going
in the topic of paramilitary disorder in the town. Because we're dealing with a regulatory process
and a licensed insurance that doesn't damage us, there's no sort of pot of money to get split up
if we succeed. If we succeed, the city gets less blood and the citizens get less blood and that's
all wonderful but you can't sort of cart office like that to hand the data's really to come and say
so we are building mostly our own. And so the total amount since 2013 that the city has paid my firm
is about 2.6 million dollars. It is a lot of money. It's not lost on this particular risk momentary
what an investment that is in this process. And one of the things we'll talk about is why it takes so much effort
in this particular analysis more than the most. But the other thing I want to say is I went back
into our economic system and looked at, you know, we have to confront discounts that we brand who typically
reduce more costs each month, but 4% of the bill. And since the start of 2020 is what I have the back to
just about a 25% discount for our standard rates. And I can tell you, that's a very large discount
and a very good-sized large, large, large, large, small, and a pay. That was close to the standard rates.
And it's because we're very good-sized or a very good-sized business is that is constantly taking twists and turns
that eat a time and effort. And we know it's a problem that the city just needs to be exactly dealing with all these issues.
So why doesn't it take so much effort? Well, one thing is, you know, charity and maybe there's a hundred million dollars
taken. This problem might be 200. You know, around $100 million is just a number of the
charities where through, I'm like, well, I'll argue within the DC circuit. It wasn't based on the evidence.
It's nothing in the record. And he just sort of threw an effort and said, if we have to do what the city's
has to do, it'll cost $100 million. And that, you know, one of the judges on the panel will need to be shot back.
Well, isn't the city losing a fortune, too, in the play? So I think they got it.
Um, G.R.E.A. tends to delay and kind of, uh, office gate. What's going on? It's in the technical studies.
And we could just want to example that, um, quickly. You know, that, changing the rules along the way,
you had started it in a couple of years ago, pushed through amendments to marks the federal power act,
applicable only to G.R.E.A.
I can't control whether or not something has been done
before, not something that is, is there a good process
and we'll talk about exactly how that came back to it.
And what's going to be a PhD in adventure?
These PhDs are busy, they have a lot going on.
Every one of them is being hired or a graduate
and it's complicated.
And they don't have limits resources.
And so they can't attention to where the speaking we
know is, you know.
And in the last round of the licensing,
that wasn't listening, and, you know,
we've been learning what the consequences
is that we need to license.
So, I'm not going to realize this.
I'm not going to talk too much about creating a group
or that's sort of been suggesting that what's going on
in human licensing.
But I will talk about how to complain about it in 2018.
Basically what we said was, the existing 1992 license
requires GREA to acquire and retain the rights
to use all land, both necessary or appropriate
for the construction, maintenance, and operation of the project.
And just so your project is defined
to include the dam and the reservoir and all the sort of related stuff.
So, hard for claim, the city's complain
can be filed in 2018, basically said,
by repeatedly flooding the land where GREA
has no rights to do so.
It is violated this license requirement.
It has not required much less to claim the right
to use that land by putting water on in order to get a better amount.
This is not what looks a lot like once,
probably most of you have seen it different times.
But this one's a little bit special.
It's one that we prepared for that 2018 complaint.
And what you've seen below represents the area
that is flooded in the 1994, let's specifically,
as calculated by Dr. Paul, and it's so it's results
from the study in the civil litigation 20 years ago.
That you heard about from Larry Gordon.
But we had the city's technical consultant take that old way
and put it into this new manner to demonstrate rapidly.
Now, the blue area isn't everywhere,
it was flooded in 1994.
It's the area that was flooded in 1994,
and has outside the boundaries of the principal project.
You see the dotted line, the white line, the red line, the red line,
the dark green.
Those areas are inside the project manner.
The journey has rights to put up.
So everything in blue is where in 1994, a long book water,
it's outside the project boundary.
And so with some exceptions, probably the vast majority
is areas where the area also doesn't have ease, but so it's empty.
And the other book water there, in that book water,
in that book, well, so we basically set up like this.
of the state court writings in Oklahoma. This is land of geria, you let it in this specific instance
that I know right to do so. And as a part of that one, it's a violation that
lies in the part of it. This is just a zoomed out version. You can see sort of the larger area
connecting some of the, you know, nearby communities and elsewhere in the county, particularly
upstream. Myod is, it's a little part of me. Myod is right here in the middle. And so you can see
all the area upstream toward a conversation age, the steps toward a bridge. It's a kind of why
I've been lying playing on them all that area, and what a more than what a man, what a man. So
when you're working really hard, I've been together. First basically dismissed the complaint
with almost no explanation. We said that's not right. As a federal agency, it was good to precede your
access. You had to, and this explained yourself when you do many pretty much as a agency, kind of who said
it didn't. We have built a Vc circuit, which is unovicious or the second highest court in the
land. The Vc circuit, we do as we were talking, that hurt totally failed to justify
a specific complaint, failed to analyze the evidence that we before. And so, we're manned in the case,
dismissed or made it in the court, or then dismissed with the complaint. And we're manned, and that's just
being said, and then headed back to third basically with some instructions to say, no, no matter
in the following ways, look at the evidence, explain what you're thinking. Excellent question. So
a little bit of a sad one. You know, we're crystal and mystery ones, and you'll hear that we are
in the mindsets too, but they're real opportunities. And I was like, when you get any time you win a
girl in the agency, people in the agency knows that people have the agency, you know, the
most senior lawyers start getting into a halt in the military proceedings. And this was not just a
appeal to a boy. You know, you're very, very, very, very excited. It's a great pain. It's a great
opinion for several reasons. One of which is extremely short. And when you get in a short opinion from
a court of appeals, it's usually because you want really good. It was an easy one, you know. And there's
a big language in the bank. You know, you're probably taking 15 to 20 minutes. They'll be some
legal easy to understand. But there's quite a bit more than most cases that I think is very clear
in common sense. It just says, there's all this evidence. Get a name and try. Come on, what are you doing?
So many minutes back. Now, how do we're licensing? The licensing process usually involves several
years of technical studies, kind of negotiation about mitigation and impacts. The regulations
that are in place, like I said, designed for a collaborative process between the licensing, the regulations
and statement orders and studies and all of this. And if it tends to get, kind of,
of a kind of jammed up with the list of CDs, and who claimed, well, as really where we've been here in the end.
Nevertheless, I'll see you in my own communities around, are going to live with the outcomes of this receiving for 30 to 50 years,
because that's how long the next license is going to last.
In fact, longer than that, because the effects from operations during that license, whether it's, you know,
the way a sentiment moves, the wouldn't look at the name of an operating differently, whether it is
social and economic impacts from people who lose a business, you know, move away after a flood, and everyone back all of that.
Those things will ripple down beyond even the 30 to 50 years of the next license is actually turned.
So the license, in order to know these things about five years,
application is due to years before the current license expires.
That can kind of be extended for a variety of reasons.
I don't know what I'm about to say.
I want to hear later.
The Pencil Mode Project, GREA, and Asked for an extension of all five years, a couple of years ago,
for a gig on a little over three.
So when we kind of stretch out the process here, in less of a year from now,
GREA will provide its full application for a science license.
The other piece of the kind of process puzzle here is this legislation that
sent it here in a push to the Congress of 2020.
That we think it's not really not very well-worded or clear,
but since it's intended to change the rules of GREA, it's better.
And only one has to go to that.
Okay, so I'm going to really try and stick quickly to these next few slides,
but only can you just want example from a technical study,
a kind of process issues that we haven't dealing with here.
And there are lots more examples than this.
I'm going to show you some technical stuff or some technical terminology.
I don't even worry too much about that.
The point to focus on is just how hard it is to get to even require GREA to do the Wednesday.
Much less actually get the results from the evaluation than what we're going to do.
So what we're going to get at here is basically a focus, right?
Just very quickly, what we're looking at is a profile of the river.
The dam is kind of here.
Springer is just as twin bridges.
City is up here.
I always, you know, in the 60th Road, that's a sports bridge.
And you're looking at a profile of the riverbomb.
The black line is where the riverbomb was.
In 1940, before the dam was built.
The blue and red lines are from surveys.
More recently, 2009, 2019, 2019.
So you can see if you work the way across here.
In 2015, your 20 feet of sediment that has raised the riverbed at the end of the dam was created.
And it's essentially, you think about a riverbed up the right way.
Where the flowing water is still one.
The sand and still.
And whatever it is, the seven of them being here
but there are tends to grow out somewhere in his solar water.
And so his area from Virginia's downstream is,
you know, depends on the time of year,
and the reason, you know, whether it flows,
but that range is roughly where the tributaries
both the spring and the ocean will empty into the reservoir.
And so you see all this seven, you know,
the point being, exactly how they have impacts
that distribution and movement of seven
is an important, a very important piece
of the total flood of the dam causes.
You can also imagine that additional height of seven,
structurally it's not like another dam,
but it acts like one in terms of just competing
with a flow of the water or the downstream.
So it tends to back up water even more
than what we get that seven had in our solar water.
So that's a long term, in fact,
of the dam's operations, causing sediment to a peculiar dam.
That it turns exacerbates the short term
of a hundred floods going forward,
as long as the seven remains.
And that's always the same, why the seven of the studies are important.
So yeah, basically, in 2018,
greater than the rising thing, actually,
this is one of the first pieces I've worked on in the great detail.
For a request of a sedimentation study,
GREA proposed one that was totally in that way
that we're allowed to have a lot of estimation techniques,
no computer modeling, which we have to prepare
since the beginning, computer models have to evaluate these challenges.
We did this right at the city team,
and our consultative tech came up with a better version
that advocated successively for ultimately agree with us
and to wire for the study,
include what's called HECRAS, you don't even worry
what that means, it's just kind of a long time.
That's the goal that we set out in 2018, HECRAS model.
It's software from the learning board of engineers
in the speed standard, and we set that to each of you
to figure out how to set them is what it will run
under the project of operations.
2019, I mentioned, we had this license extension.
So, oh, an interesting thing.
So, HECRAS said, yes, do what the city said,
do that HECRAS model, and that starts the clock
on the first year of the year, these studies,
at the end of which they're in the final initial study,
with their initial results.
Before that year is up, we get into the license extension,
which is a whole series of stories of its own.
We don't need to go into them right now,
but it's a place to say, the license got scratched out
by three years during year one,
and the initial study deadline would.
So, GRDA had almost three years to finish it.
It's initial report from the study year one.
That deadline that became the last September.
We got their initial report from some occasion,
as well as a whole day.
want to take those studies. You don't mind us, which is just one example from one study.
After nearly three years of work on this, there's that mutation report, no handwriting
model, no model results. They put it what they call the interim study report, which unlike
initial study report, interim study report is not a term that's in the regulations anywhere.
It's just something they made out of. So I got this interim study report and the interim study report
has the sedimentation study was completely completed in accordance with first directions.
Well, except for one variance in schedule. They said the hacker's model is in development.
They said, we expect to file the shared model, we'll stay focused on the report,
and I'm going to calibrate it to make sure it works.
Expect to file that by the end of 2020, we'll have three months later.
The city asked for a set for their comments on the model.
You know, later, when they filed a complaint,
Giri had a post, I would request it for a set of late comments on the late model.
Three weeks after that, Giri had filed a report along with their responses to other comments on the time of the series.
Then it was a maintenance switch.
I mean, again, no model results. Again, no model. Instead, what we got was a new statement proposal that would
be implemented in the model and all together, claiming it would be impossible because of some
sampling results about the sedimentation actually that we're doing.
We claim the hacker as a can't work. Of course, they've posted it all along.
So the city spent a bunch of time and studied with the experts,
putting comments together and explaining why yes, hacker as can't still work.
Giri A in responding to the comments and hiring a hot-sided consultant to perform what's called
a technical review. I'd love to be all for Giri A's independent review of a freeze at
Giri A, finally, what's that? Another new statement plan.
They're going to do that at Giri A's modeling.
That brings us up to just about a month or two ago.
So we still haven't had a model, we still haven't had a result.
I guess we'll see it in the year two stages of results when they've had almost four years as opposed
to all the leader going to see it.
And then they may, to be fair, they need to have good teams working on this stuff.
To an extent, it's hard to understand. Sometimes, exactly why these things go the way they do.
But it's pious to say, this is another process that's meant to work.
And it's taking a lot of extra string around. Just to get Giri A on board, we decided
that the city has set all along. And for that matter, we need to get rid of it,
because it's not a regular model. So I'm going to go away too long.
Anyway, just quickly, in the meantime, we have this legislation considered in
how in 2020, you basically go through provisions that alter aspects of the federal system.
of our act, only with what's called Project.
It was done irregularly from a sexual point of view
of the European Union, and one of the art services
committee in the New Chair.
There was no caring.
Instead, it was added to the bill.
It happened to the committee.
It was done to the door.
That's part of us, or on the bus.
Set of amendments that the public managers
and amendments, these amendments,
because it was the chair committee.
So he answered those after the committee's work is done.
And here's one of the things where I wrote the city's understanding.
I should say that it's my understanding
and my college of business, right?
I'm very aware.
And we could debate it to the city, but.
What we understand is that instead of not actually
held up, the ultimate passage of this must
pass, multi-thousand-paying, natural-to-beth policy act,
until the house was exact.
This sort of special individual, for every legislation,
just to change the federal power act that has pulled up.
So it has to, now I just think of what next.
Jerry, basically, claims that the effect is that it's no longer accountable
for major chunks of what the firm needs to agree with it.
It says Congress will remove the firm
according to a direct planning, or otherwise control a lot of levels of the project.
The city disagrees.
But maybe this is saying Jerry is playing net, net,
but overall it's worth it.
Further reports are not put into it, but yet that's not also
in the second half of the licensing.
So the point I guess in that story is that Jerry
was all ready to make any licensing, especially
along the part of the city, as a participant.
So it did not make it that much longer and harder by passing this
though, because now the city has the way and what the legal effect
of this kind of strange legislation is.
And then even we do that.
We still have to go through the whole licensing process,
under the new rules of the road, if they are in fact
as it led in just a year.
So that's just a couple of little slices of the
licensing process to try to do a censor.
Why do I want it so far?
Why do I want it so much more to get this done?
But that's all I have for you tonight, but I'd be asking more questions about
better or better power regulation.
Thank you, Robert.
Thank you.
I don't know.
You can pick that one.
I think it's safe to say that for a capital money
that we spend with the energy is in money.
What do we have to force you to do that?
You go back and do new things that further
back and do it together.
Some reason, further, further and further.
So we have to constantly build up more money to get
them to do the things in there.
Why would you buy a license?
And then, this isn't going to be normal.
I don't want to point out my bad tune in the comment.
There's a lot of misleading and inaccurate information
around town lately.
That's not my accident.
Please, if you hear something, then you
want to have a question.
You know, I'm bad at the post, but I'm
absolutely bad at the post.
We'll give it to you guys in the start
of the ability to do it.
We've got Jack Diola.
It does the problem with this guy.
Everybody got just the son of a man.
That's so good.
If you have questions, please, please let us know.
We'll get you a question.
Thank you.
Absolutely.
Thank you all all for tonight for your presentation.
For time, if you're putting this together, you're traveling.
You need to learn.
You need to need information to be shared.
It's been a long time since we've had this subject to me.
So this is really important.
I have a very serious issue on that.
I also want to make that the slide to the goal of seeing tonight
will be available online as well as the complete video
of tonight's presentation.
As well as the hearing, we're ready to do it.
So with that being said, this includes the presentation
for our meeting tonight, we are definitely
going to be running on, but we're going to get in a certain yellow
one taking away from the community's opportunity to do it.
So that being said, what we're going to do is we're going to ask anyone
that wants to ask a question or simply make a statement.
We're going to have to go online to start by letting that go
on the inside.
All the way down here for the start, just come to the point
that we're going to want to, and of course, we don't want to say
that we might have put a statement in the box of this view.
So, stating for the minutes of the view there,
he has a sheet of paper where we're going to ask him
right the name, your address, the book, right in the view.
And then you're coming to the center stage and asking the question
we're going to ask, he's going to ask one question,
if you want to statement, you're going to have to read the time.
So that we can give everybody the ones to speak and all the time.
So that after that three minutes, we're going to have
to go back to the end of the view if you want to, if you want to make
a statement or ask a question, just simply go to the end line
and go back to the way it should turn.
Other than that, our goal, of course, is to give a community
an opportunity to voice a certain answer to questions.
Council here, we've got a great experts here, and we want to
give you a better statement.
Also, we can go to the end of the view.
So we're going to be running a little about the problem 9 for the
,,,
to go ahead and say, oh, go to the rest of the group for three minutes,
taking you to the challenge, we're going to go through the process,
and maybe ask you to do it.
I don't suspect we'll have any other challenge.
So let's take this for a change.
So we'll have that.
We'll look for any one that needs to look like,
comment on our questions.
I don't know why I haven't been inside the group.
If we're already a question for the comments,
I've got a list that we gathered online,
and we have a variety of other events.
I've seen being able to write it on the first,
so we can get your answers.
It should be my challenge.
I was just wondering,
if someone could give us kind of a bigger dive in,
or if it was half or more,
but seven, forty-five, and then seven, fifty-five,
or seven, five, seven, five, seven, six,
and then we have a really nice dive.
In the management of the lay blood,
I think, four, and in the year,
it does have something to say something to do,
and they're not, they're certain.
Keep these kind of break it down, don't break it down,
when you control those from here and there.
had one thing, so the elevation is 7.45 and 7.55 and that's 7.45. I'm very
89 percent generalities. That's why I'm new on this aspect. At 7.45, 4 if it is
anticipated, it will become bugs that will be gone. If the core does have the ability to
start regularly, it will be released by opening data points. There's always the ability
to judge them back, but it's an anticipation of the course of 7.45 or natural reaching 7.45
and the core does have the right and does have the ability to read them. Basically, it's
a core, because I mean, that two ways a lot gets through the name and through the power
of the name. The core would be much to one direction and make it open. It's true. When you
get the key out of the name of the name, it's true. Here it is, the rule always wants to
decide it's to pay, and that's not really false. That increases vibration, increases the
ability of generating power. Point that out of the name, put the state of civil and huge. Here
it is a major choice to operate the name with that restriction. That's why I read that
really opinion from why it now, where a basic attack with the core is directly given that context
is not going to be in my ability to accept certain relationships, in any way that the name is called
one direction. I would have one thing, which is that there is absolutely right at the core
right on those circumstances, the right, what operations. As a practical matter, there's not a lot of
transparency, there are anything. One thing we hope to get a better sense of all of your name is
exactly how to look at how to detail. What is the level of specificity that the core
is directly in the goes operations that? Because it's not all clear if they're giving to
any expression that they're a cleverness, it's just passed for instance, it may well be interested
in it as some flexibility in one of the core instructions. I also say a story I didn't tell
what was about G-R-D-A's home model to predict what operations is very mad at circulating
actual operations that we see between 2007 and 2007 and G-R-D-A before. It's not a clear one,
either one, it's their own operations so important. It was a six-month point to get hold of them,
but the reality is one thing, the reality is another thing, there's a lot of blackness
right here.
I think one of the great residents was talking about some of it.
Some of it, well, man, and they didn't see that way.
They came up.
So they didn't have that.
I need to speak.
Please come over here, so we can come back and raise something.
So what I mean, actually is like that.
You don't have to worry about something like that.
Yeah.
I was a man on the stage.
I'm here and I want my mom to enjoy skating.
I want her to be strong, man.
Here are all different presentations.
We're very helpful.
We're being left in, kind of the brain.
I'm going to put all this together.
My mom would get involved in the second class.
And I'm here in town.
So they try to help him.
And what I got out of tonight was one of my expectations.
And I was thinking one of the lines was why I needed to gather in order for her to be
a woman who saw those children in the same place.
But what I realized is, you guys are quite a bunch of people.
And I'm really appreciate it.
Because I don't want to do anything in my home.
Now it was our house that I grew up in, which he's 80 years old.
She doesn't have the ability to live in her own life.
I haven't used to living down to work.
Part of this emotional plea that I heard so much of from our members of this community.
I think that you're up here.
I'm not going to need anything to go right now.
I think you're all talking.
I beg you guys to continue this life.
I beg you, RDA.
Do not make it.
I don't have a house to resort.
Thank you.
And I want to thank you guys for coming.
And I learned a lot.
And I saw two things I saw on this street.
And it upset me.
One was a club in 1988.
And another one was a club in 2004.
With a club in SMG and SMC.
I called the city and I asked.
I don't know what I'm going to do, and the person didn't know.
I don't really really didn't know.
She said they asked the names.
We didn't have any names on that case.
They called it to ask.
And then they didn't know so much.
They just kind of up to the back of their house a little bit.
We're not going to work.
I would have to work.
And I got all of the bridge of the street leader.
And saw the street leader in the town.
And I turned around and went mad.
I was through three years every time I was alone.
The other thing that I've said to me was,
our house was up there.
And then he said, I heard six of them.
He said, six houses.
He had my name.
I don't think any of us understood that they had their name.
They had their name.
They called it like, we lost names.
We lost names.
And we lost names.
And I want to fight with these guys.
But that, that, it's not like it will never be mine.
Because we're just done with it.
We're going to be on the right.
Still trying to think things through.
And it's still going around this because of it.
Okay.
We're going to go back to the house.
So I'm just going to be in the control of the panel and have a minute and I'll sit in.
Maybe some of your questions.
So I'll start just in the top here.
I will be in the end of the course of the nation.
Why was the late death in Berlin?
Are you efficient in the end?
Or in the end?
Can you see the end?
The water in.
Everybody have the image of that.
You want to go to the changing room?
You know, I can take it.
So the initial term of the day and I'm had that contract.
Yes, so that it's on the loop.
Or that it's much lower.
As I showed it on my slides.
How could it be here?
There's a 7-7-4-7-7-5 in there.
Because it requires the result of that contract.
That contract can be that 21.
So maybe the least that it isn't about you.
It's a hiring the elevation of the water.
The water.
and then the pressure there is a detergent, which makes it spend faster, which makes it very important.
So, Jerry A. Oh, it's once the light gets high as it can possibly be, the maximum is that heavy.
So, it's still as the partial level of the issue, on the side of the body.
And in 1982, they didn't even start the grants, but they ended it and went to the bank, and ended it in 2017.
And they could take a little of the work license.
If you say it down to your brother, there's nobody that's going to protect us at the same time.
And this next license, like we will have, will allow a dearer to run it anytime, anytime, anywhere they want to, up to 745.
So, that will be, it's starting to play in other areas.
I'm going to, like, let's show another time, the way the old nation is higher.
I'm going to write some of this to the 2nd control of the capacity.
And then, it should work to the 7th of the day.
I'll just have 1, 1, 2, 1, and that issue.
Based on the discussion I gave about 7th patient.
And that's any time you've got enough of a flow that you're starting to get that backwater back.
If 4th, 7th, as a Q2, it will be done.
I can add, you know, a delta, each together, and by with ridges, where that 7th gets a drop out.
And that delta, the same low flow is going to have a little more whack on our screen.
So that could be a new feedback too.
I don't know, possibly not a good flow, possibly.
And at least it's easy to do this then.
So the next is actually just to work to stay in the question.
It reads, it might be interesting, you know, we are in the end, we have to stay in the end,
and then we go to the quantitative studies that correlate very well in common and ask to play.
We're not related in this place, because it doesn't exist.
In terms of how much future you have to look and not so great in the 7th or 5th control.
If I could respond a little bit, which is there's a 7th patient study.
I mean, it's a socioeconomic study.
Also, it's part of the relationship.
And what we have to make is not one of the city's or flat areas.
We have to invest in the 7th and in trying to attach any rivers.
And it's disappointingly not very nice enough.
And actually, much less than the methods than any of that's a much of a unique impact on socioeconomic.
Just to be clear, none of our own future is focused on something.
I can't even get back.
But study itself has a digital map.
That's the focus, you know.
It really is expensive, but that's a lot of people who are working on this research.
It's also a common sense.
I don't even know why I'm sorry, okay, I just don't know.
But we still don't know what to do.
I just got it with taxes every time.
And all the things that we've described by the Google department...
... that's how it looks like.
I don't know what I'm gonna say.
It was totally accurate, and all the other people helped it.
And one of the things that I said didn't say
that the positives of the state, for the year I ate
or other way, the negatives for my help.
Can't believe I would say could they recognize the negatives if I had them?
They didn't even go that far to end up finding that their warning is in my hand.
Another way to get the study is, again, they asked the questions that allowed them to say,
because they were, to areas, they were each time.
And they said, there was no way to get them.
They didn't even identify them.
Because of the way the study criteria was gone.
And I think what should have been written was a question.
I don't know if the evidence I would give you that question.
One was, is there an evidence I would give?
Or the evidence?
It's called the product.
It's responsible.
It's a GRA, a group of creates many, many jobs.
It was a great evidence.
It's a statement.
The statement is issued.
The evidence.
So I'd accept that that question.
For example, if what you get in the water, in there, you know,
providing a better study of the land and doing the push of purpose.
Why?
A little bit of a question.
What's that?
Because it is a hybrid of what's going to be raised in the water.
That's it.
So that this is a relevant message.
It's the insidious data response.
Here, the A is basically maximizing the back water effect as it is.
They can make it a little bit more.
That little bit more is good.
It's not another analysis.
It's good.
It's not another piece.
It's in the water.
But in the sake, it won't enough so much, and they still passed.
Exactly.
It needs some longer news.
I think it was the relevant evidence, but it's a little less.
And then it, it's a evidently a conscious return.
There's some moment.
But as I experienced in a sort of an axoline.
We did our raising, we could put it in a separate part of that.
We looked at a line of room and then we noticed that it was at the same.
That would slightly make it worse because now you don't have to go into something through
something.
But before it's like something to do, it's like something to do.
It's going to make it more like...